Guide to the Paul C. Edwards Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Paul C. Edwards papers
1895-1986
1912-1962
SC0170
Edwards, Paul C., (Paul Carroll), 1882-1962.
7 Linear feet
These papers largely pertain to Edwards' professional career and to his administrative positions with Stanford University. Papers relating to Stanford, 1940-1986, include correspondence and supporting documents from his tenure on the Board of Trustees (1943-1962), especially during his term as president, 1948-53; articles about Edwards; and a file of correspondence with Profs. Harold Fisher and Ernest Hilgard, 1952-1954. Professional papers include his speeches, essays, and editorials; original poetry and plays; and extensive correspondence with other journalists and newspaper editors. Correspondents include Alfred O. Anderson, 1910-1937; Will B. Colver, 1920-1925; Roy Howard, 1921-1956; E. T. Leech, 1919-1922; Lowell Mellett, 1926-1931; Robert F. Paine, 1909-1929; E. W. Scripps, 1911-1917; Robert P. Scripps, 1919-1932; Max Stern, 1924-1932; and Basil Woon, 1917-1919. Also included are several childhood letters by Edwards, 1895-1896; high school essays, 1901-1903; letters pertaining to a student prank at Stanford, 1908; and his typescript memoirs.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of Paul C. Edwards, Jr. and Carroll Edwards Ammen, 1977; and Carroll Becket, 1995.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Paul C. Edwards studied journalism at Stanford from 1902-1906 and went on to become, successively, reporter, city editor, and managing editor of the San Francisco News. After a few years working as editor on the Dallas Dispatch, and as founding editor on the Houston Press, the Scripps-Howard Newspapers made him Southwestern Group editor-in-chief in 1919 and, in 1922, head of the California Group. In 1925 he became editor of the San Diego Sun. From 1932 to 1956, he served as associate editor of the San Francisco News.
Mr. Edwards took an active interest in Stanford affairs, serving in the 1930s and 1940s as chairman of the Annual Appeal Committee of the Stanford Fund, as a member of the Board of Governors of the Stanford Associates, and as President of the Associates beginning on October 28, 1941. In October of 1943 he was appointed to the Stanford Board of Trustees. He served as President of the Board from May 1948 until October 1953 when he was elected trustee emeritus.
Description of the Collection
These papers largely pertain to Edwards' professional career and to his administrative positions with Stanford University. Papers relating to Stanford, 1940-1986, include correspondence and supporting documents from his tenure on the Board of Trustees (1943-1962), especially during his term as president, 1948-53; articles about Edwards; and a file of correspondence with Profs. Harold Fisher and Ernest Hilgard, 1952-1954. Professional papers include his speeches, essays, and editorials; original poetry and plays; and extensive correspondence with other journalists and newspaper editors. Correspondents include Alfred O. Anderson, 1910-1937; Will B. Colver, 1920-1925; Roy Howard, 1921-1956; E. T. Leech, 1919-1922; Lowell Mellett, 1926-1931; Robert F. Paine, 1909-1929; E. W. Scripps, 1911-1917; Robert P. Scripps, 1919-1932; Max Stern, 1924-1932; and Basil Woon, 1917-1919. Also included are several childhood letters by Edwards, 1895-1896; high school essays, 1901-1903; letters pertaining to a student prank at Stanford, 1908; and his typescript memoirs.
Access Terms
Anderson, Alfred O.; Colver, William B.; Crothers, George E. (George Edward), 1870-1957.; Davis, Paul H.; Dinkelspiel, Lloyd W.; Ditz, George A.; Edwards, Paul C., (Paul Carroll), 1882-1962.; Eurich, Alvin C., (Alvin Christian), 1902-1987.; Fisher, Harold H. (Harold Henry), 1890-1975; Hilgard, Ernest R. (Ernest Ropiequet), 1904-2001; Howard, Roy Wilson, 1883-1964.; Jacobson, David S.; Leech, Edward Towner, 1892-; Lillick, Ira S.; Manspeaker, Alfred F.; Mellett, Lowell, 1884-1960.; Morrell, George.; Paine, Robert Finley, 1856-; Scripps, E. W. (Edward Wyllis), 1854-1926.; Scripps, Robert Paine.; Scripps-Howard Newspapers.; Stanford Research Institute.; Stanford University. Board of Trustees.; Stanford University. Stanford Associates.; Sterling, J. E. Wallace, (John Ewart Wallace), 1906-1985; Stern, Max William, 1884-1950.; Tresidder, Donald Bertrand, 1894-1948; Walker, Frank Fish, 1896-1978; Wilbur, Ray L., (Ray Lyman), 1875-1949; Woon, Basil, 1893-1974; Journalism --United States.; Universities and colleges--Administration.
Collection Contents
- Incoming Correspondence, Series 1
  - Adams, Jack, 1943 November 18 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allen, Riley, 1943 December 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Anderson, Eleanor, 1962 January 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bailey, Morton, 1942 February 16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Barkan, Hans, 1941 October 20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bean, Donald P., 1948 June 7 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Beeson, Albert P., 1942 January 6 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Behrens, Squire, 1942 November 7 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bennet, Merrill K., 1942 October 17 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Blosser, Ray W., 1942 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Blyth, Charles R., 1950 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Boyd, E. Forrest, 1951 February 12 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brandt, Karl, 1947 January 11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Breer, Carl, 1949 July 28 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brewer, William, 1943 November 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brooke, Banner R., 1942 February 25 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brown, Leland H., 1948 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brucato, John G., 1948 May 19 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Burbank, D. W., 1942 July 24 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bush, Chilton, 1942 Feburary 4 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Byler, Olivia, 1941 September 16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Carlson, Donald T., 1961 August 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Carmody, Frank, 1948 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Carpenter, Thomas, 1947 January 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Carter, E. Finley, 1957 January 8 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Caughey, R. E., 1942 May 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chance, Ruth (Mrs. Jackson), 1962 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Christopher, W. M., 1948 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clark, Addison N., 1943 October 17 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Coetz, A. M., 1951 November 27 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Combiths, Elizabeth, 1943 January 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Coombs, Edward, 1942 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Copp, Andrew J. Jr., 1948 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cosovich, Jon C., 1963 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cottrell, Edwin, 1942 July 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cowley, W. H., 1951 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Craemer, Justus F., 1942 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Crary, Robert, 1942 May 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Crothers, George E., 1948 July 2 - 1951 May 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cuthbertson, Kenneth M., 1960 May 3 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cutter, Leland W., 1948 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Davis, H. William Hawley, 1942 August 5 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Davis, J. S., 1943 October 20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - DeLisle, Frank F., 1943 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - DeRoos, Robert, 1948 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Deutsch, Monroe E., 1943 October 22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dey, Ben, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dinkelspiel, Lloyd, 1938 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ditz, George A., 1941 - 1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Douglas, Chesley M., 1942 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Douglas, Earl S., 1949 June 16 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Doyle, Morris N., 1948 May (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Drugan, Frank, 1943 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dryer, George W., 1941 October 28 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - DuBridge, L. A., 1948 December 20 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Davis, Paul H., 1941 September 18 - 1951 December 17 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Elliot, Harold F., 1942 September 22 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Erwin, E. S., 1944 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Estler, William C., 1952 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Eurich, Alvin, 1944 October 26 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Falk, Adrien J., 1948 August 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faulkner, Hozel Pedlar, 1943 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Faust, Clarence, 1949 March 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fisher, H. H., 1948 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fowler, B., 1942 October 8 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Freeman, Blanche, 1950 December 19 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fuller, Adeline, 1928 June 19 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Garfias, V. R., 1942 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gauyard, Leslie N., 1943 October 20 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gerry, Martin H.,III, 1948 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gibson, Weldon, 1942 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Glover, Fred, 1960 June 29 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gordon, Mrs. Ruth, 1942 Spetember 10 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Graham, Chalmers G., 1948 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Griffin, Willard C., 1943 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Guerard, Mrs. Albert, 1948 April 15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Guggenhime, Richard E., 1962 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gunst, Morgan A., 1942 March 24 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Guthrie, Frank D., 1943 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hailey, H. W., 1943 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hanna, Paul, "The Betrayal of America", a Complaint to the California Legislature regarding subversive textbooks and curriculum practices in public schools., 1947 March (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Harper, William P., 1942 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Harrison, Raymond D., 1942 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Heller, Mrs. Edward A., 1961 May 15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Henley, Mrs. Lloyd, 1942 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hicks, W. Wesley, 1942 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Holden, Paul E., Gantt Medalist, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Howard, Lowry, 1942 April 24 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Howard, Roy, 1943 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Howell, John: correspondence re Bible Collection, between Herbert Hoover, J. Howell (and others), 1934-1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hyatt, Mrs. Edward Jr., 1942 March (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ingram, K. C., 1943 October 18 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hoover, Herbert H., 1942-1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Jackson, David S., 1942 April 6 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Jackson, Hugh, 1942 September 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Johnston, Paul, 1948 May 28 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Jones, Richard F., 1948 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, David S., 1942 July 20 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, Jessie K., Mrs. David, 1951 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, Knight Starr, 1943 November 3 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Jorgenson, H. G., 1942 April 8 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kalenborn, Mrs. A. S., 1943 October 19 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kellogg, William S., 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lillick, Ira S., 1948 May 24 - 1951 October 22 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mackintosh, Kenneth, 1941 September 18 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - McCann-Erickson, Inc., 1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - McClanahan, Janet M., 1942 October 22 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - McCombs, Philip N., 1943 December 10 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - McCutcheon, Thomas, Matthews, Griffiths and Greene, 1948 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - McKee, Paul B., 1948 August 16 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - McLaine, Bonnie C., 1942 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Manspeaker, Alfred E., 1948 August 25 - 1951 July 10 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Marble, John E., 1941 September 19 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Marble, John M., 1942 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Marshall, James B., (manager engineering dept of Marsh and McClennan), 1950 May 5 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Martin, Irving, 1948 May 26 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Marts, Arnaud (New York Times), 1942 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Masters, Alfred F., 1942 May 7 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mears, Eliot G., comment on Person's Report "Public Relations at Stanford", 1942 August 19 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Merner, Garfield D., 1948 May 25 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Michel, L. B., 1948 May 22 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Millet, Ralph, 1943 November 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Millikan, Robert A., 1948 December 17 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mirrielees, Miss Edith R. (Mrs. P. F. Zelver, assistant to), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mitchell, J. P., 1942 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Morgan, Byron, 1948 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Morris, Samuel B., 1942 October 31 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mudd, Seeley, G., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Mumford, Lewis (from minutes of Trustees meeting), 1947 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Morell, George, 1958 March - 1950 November 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Naftzger, Roy E., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Norwood, Vivian W., 1948 May 27 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Nute, James C., 1942 August 7 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - O'Gara, Gerald J., 1948 May 25 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Osborne, George E., 1943 November (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Parker, G. B., 1943 November 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Parks, Doris A., 1950 January 17 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Parsons, Edward L., 1948 May 23 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Peck, Templeton, 1948 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Persons, C. E., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Petree, Neil, 1943 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Phleger, Herman, 1948 April 12 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Polhemus, James H., 1942 January 5 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Reynolds, Harry B., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Reynolds, Herbert K., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Reynolds, Jim, 1952 May 25 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Ribble, F. D. G., 1952 January 15 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Richman, Frederick I., 1951 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Robinson, Edgar E., 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Schank, F. R., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Schwartz, Marchmont, letters regarding his reappointment as head football coach, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sheldon, Irene B., 1942 December 8 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Shelton, James E., 1942 May 26 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Shoup, Jack W., 1948 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sloss, Leon, Jr., 1942 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Mrs. Alfred J., 1942 August 28 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Dick, 1943 October 19 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Everett, 1941 July 30 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Ray, 1943 January 6 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Spencer, Eldridge T., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Spragens, Thomas A., 1949 March 22 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stalnaker, John M., 1948 May 14 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stamm, Edward A., 1942 August 20 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stanley, Leo, 1942 April (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sterling, Ann, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sterling, Wallace, 1948 December 16 - 1961 March 17 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Storey, Parnie H., 1942 April 27 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Storey, Thomas A., 1941 July 3 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Stoss, Mrs., undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Swain, Robert E., 1943 October 18 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Swim, Dudley H., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Taylor, C. V., 1942 October 23 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Teitsworth, C. S., 1942 June 5 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Thelen, Max, 1948 May 22 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Thomas, Katherine Nash, 1942 May 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Treat, Jess, 1943 October 20 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Tresidder, Donald B., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Tresidder, Mary Curry, 1949 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Vanderpoel, Blanche, P. B., 1950 January 16 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - VanPatten, Nathan, 1942 August 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Vernier, Hazel A., 1942 April 24 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Vincenti, Louis R., 1948 May 28 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Wagner, George, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Wakefield, Fay C., 1942 November 16 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Walker, Frank, 1941 November 21 - 1950 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Warren, Earl, 1953 December 17 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Weinman, L. R., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Wert, Robert J., Stanford Convalescent Home correspondence: 10/26/51, Land Development Council correspondence: 4/11/52, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - White, Lynn, Jr., 1942 August 18 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Whitman, Fred, 1962 January 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, 1941 October 4 - 1949 March 3 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Winbigler, H. D., 1942 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Yost, Mary, 1948 May (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dave (Bauxart), undated (possibly 1943) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - John, W. D., 1943 October 18 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Outgoing Correspondence, Series 2
  - Storey, Dr. and Mrs. Thomas A., 1941 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bacon, William C., 1941 November 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, 1941 November 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Polhemus, James H. (memoranda to), 1942 January 12 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bailey, Morton, 1942 February 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ditz, George A., 1942 Feburary 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Van Sooy, Neal, 1942 Feburary 13 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cooper, Mrs. John, 1942 March 16 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Members of the Stanford Associates, 1942 March 24 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Associates, Mrs., 1942 April 3 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Paul H., 1942 April 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Members of Stanford Associates, 1942 April 21 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Kimpton, L. A., 1942 April 21 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Howard, Lowry S., 1942 April 21 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Jackson, George B., 1942 April 21 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Macfarland, John C., 1942 April 22 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Goodan, Roger, 1942 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Naftzger, Roy E., 1942 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Stanley, Leo L., 1942 April 29 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ditz, George A., 1942 May 9 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Masters, Al, 1942 May 9 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Caughey, Reginald E., 1942 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Members of Stanford Associates, 1942 May 7 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Members of the Board of Governors, 1942 July 9 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Reppy, Roy V., 1942 August 12 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Everett R., 1942 August 12 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Abbott, Jr., Frank H., 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bishop, Eugene, 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Crary, Robert C., 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Ingram, K. C., 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - James, Norris E., 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - McClanahan, E. J., 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Reynolds, Herbert K., 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Russell, Richard A., 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Shoup, Jack W., 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Richard C., 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Thrash, Jesse, 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, 1942 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Tresidder, Donald B., 1942 September 28 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Reynolds, Herbert K., 1942 October 5 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Walker, Frank F., 1942 October 7 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Sheldon, Irene B., 1942 December 9 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Tresidder, Donald B. (memo to), 1943 November 15 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Osborne, George, 1943 December 15 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Walker, Frank, 1946 January 7 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Paul H., 1948 March (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mudd, Seeley G., 1948 April 6 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Miller, C. O. G., 1948 April 6 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Sloss, Mrs. M. C., 1948 April 6 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Goodan, May Chandler, 1948 April 14 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Copp, Jr., Andrew J., 1948 April 23 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Rebecca H., 1948 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Miller, C. O. G., 1948 May 28 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Blosser, Raymond W., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Brown, H., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Brucato, John G., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Christopher, W. M., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Deutsch, Monroe, 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Guerard, Mrs. Albert L., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Holmes, Herbert, 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Jacobson, David S., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Kellogg, William S., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Lutz, Ralph, 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Martin, Irving, 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Mickel, L. B., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Norwood, Vivian W., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Roseberry, L. H., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Rothwell, Easton, 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Shoup, J. W., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Stalnaker, John M., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Thelen, Max, 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Walker, Frank F., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Wilbur, R. L., 1948 June 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - DeRoos, Robert, 1948 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Hicks, W. Wesley, 1948 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lee, Jr., Ivy, 1948 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Parsons, Edward L., 1948 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Peck, T., 1948 June 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Carmody, Frank, 1948 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Masters, Alfred R., 1948 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Merner, Garfield D., 1948 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - O'Gara, Gerald J., 1948 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Roth, Almon E., 1948 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Rothwell, Easton, 1948 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Yost, Mary, 1948 June 4 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Jordon, Mrs. David S., 1948 June 10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lillick, Ira S., 1948 June 10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Rogers, Clarence A., 1948 June 10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Thor M., 1948 June 10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Swim, H. Dudley, 1948 June 10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bean, Donald P., 1948 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Fisher, H. H., 1948 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Levit, Bert, 1948 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Graham, Chalmers G., 1948 June 23 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dinkelspiel, Lloyd, 1948 June 25 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Davis, Paul H., 1948 June 29 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mudd, Seeley G., 1948 July 8 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Walker, Frank F., 1948 August 6 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Wickett, Fred A., 1948 August 6 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Hoover, Herbert H., 1948 August 7 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Roseberry, L. H., 1948 August 27 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - McKee, Paul B., 1948 September 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mudd, Seeley G., 1948 September 27 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Mudd, Seeley G., 1948 October 4 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Kellogg, William S., 1948 October 27 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Crothers, George C., 1948 November 8 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1948 December 6 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lillick, Ira S., 1948 December 7 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Millikan, Robert A., 1948 December 14 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - DuBridge, Lee A., 1948 December 17 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1948 December 18 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Millikan, Robert A., 1948 December 22 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - DuBridge, Lee A., 1949 January 6 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Millikan, Robert A., 1949 January 6 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1949 January 9 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1949 January (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1949 January 24 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Wilbur, R. L., 1949 March 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Ditz, George A., 1949 March 19 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Martin, Ernest G., 1949 April 19 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Blyth, Charles R., 1949 April 19 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Breer, Carl, 1949 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tresidder, Mary Curry, 1949 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Douglass, Earl S., 1949 July 8 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Johnston, Paul C., 1949 August 4 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dorsey, George, 1949 September 12 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Walker, Frank F., 1949 October 10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lundberg, Louis B., 1949 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Weinmann, L. R., 1950 April 28 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Naftzger, Roy E., 1950 May 30 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1950 October 20 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Crary, Allan H., 1950 November 17 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Schank, F. R., 1950 November 27 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Jordan, Mrs. David S., 1951 January 15 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Schwartz, Marchmont, 1951 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Richman, Frederick T., 1951 May 21 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Richman, Frederick T., 1951 June 19 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Maillard, Jr., J. Ward, 1951 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sheldon, Edwin R., 1951 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace, 1951 September 11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lillick, Ira S., 1951 October 25 (Box 2, Folder 6)